{
    "subject": "resource/Joachim_Fernandez",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Senegal",
    "human_readable": "Joachim Fernandez was born in Senegal.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8755906820297241,
            "question": "Where was Joachim Fernandez born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8418042659759521,
            "question": "Has Joachim Fernandez ever traveled outside of Senegal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8252640962600708,
            "question": "What year was Joachim Fernandez born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6973864436149597,
            "question": "What nationality is Joachim Fernandez?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5288723707199097,
            "question": "What is Joachim Fernandez known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4234429597854614,
            "question": "What is Joachim Fernandez's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37013018131256104,
            "question": "Does Joachim Fernandez have any siblings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3168547749519348,
            "question": "Does Joachim Fernandez have any children?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19482387602329254,
            "question": "What language does Joachim Fernandez speak?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19369076192378998,
            "question": "What are some of Joachim Fernandez's hobbies?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Joachim Fernandez was born in Senegal.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8213_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What language does Joachim Fernandez speak?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8213_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Joachim Fernandez have any children?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8213_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Joachim Fernandez have any siblings?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8213_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8213_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8213_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8213_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8213_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8213_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8213_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8213_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8213_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8213_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8213_5.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the required JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis is because all three documents provide information that confirms Joachim Fernandez's birthplace as Senegal."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents state that \"Joachim Fernandez was born on December 6, 1972, in Ziguinchor, Senegal,\" which supports the statement that Joachim Fernandez was born in Senegal."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}